<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://conventional-branch.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://conventional-branch.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://conventional-branch.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://conventional-branch.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About The Conventional Branch specification is inspired by Conventional Commits.&#xA;Tooling for Conventional Branch commit-check: Commit Check supports checking commit messages, branch naming, committer name/email, commit signoff, customizing error messages, suggested commands and more. commit-check-action: A Github Action for checking commit message formatting, branch naming, committer name, email, commit signoff and more. VSCode Conventional Branch: Add Conventional Branch supports for VSCode. Projects Using Conventional Branch commit-check: Supports checking commit messages, branch naming, committer name/email, commit signoff, customizing error messages, suggested commands and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://conventional-branch.github.io/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://conventional-branch.github.io/posts/</guid>
      <description>Conventional Branch 1.0.0 Summary The Conventional Branch specification to define a branch based workflow for your project. When you map your workflow to branch types, you can ensure that branches are named consistently by configuring which branch types to make available. We&amp;rsquo;ve suggested some branch prefixes you might want to use but you can also specify your own naming convention. A consistent naming convention makes it easier to identify branches by type.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
